# CHRIS ALLEN MADRIAGA



#### **Contact**

#### Address:

Mariwasa St. Pipindan, Binangonan, Rizal

#### Phone:

0997 681 5214

#### Email:

madriagachrisallen21@gmail.com

#### Portfolio:

https://allenmadriaga.netlify.app

## **Technical Skills**

HTML5

CSS3

**JavaScript** 

**Bootstrap** 

**SCSS** 

Git

WordPress

Adobe XD

**AEM Sites** 

JCR

Java

#### Summary

Focused Software Developer with 4 years of working experience on developing dynamic websites. Worked on both backend and front end with willingness to learn new technology. 3 years working experience on Adobe Experience Manager Sites.

# **Skill Highlights**

- Teamwork
- Good Communication Skills
- Problem Solver

Time Management

## **Experience**

Front End Web Developer Intern – April 2019 – July 2019 Front End Web Developer – May 2020 – January 2021 Mindblow Internet Ideas Inc, Mandaluyong

- Convert PSD designs to Responsive WordPress Themes
- Work with senior developer to manage complex design projects.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- Handle multiple projects on fast paced work environment
- Managed to finish assigned task on deadline

Software Engineer - Accenture - February 2021 - Present

- Worked as an AEM Developer
- Create functional dynamic components
- Applied Agile Methodology
- Deliver User Stories on time and with quality
- Fix production bugs assigned
- Review team member pull requests
- Provide KT sessions on new team members and providing technical approaches on new components

#### **Education**

Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering - 2020 University of Rizal System – Morong Campus

## **Certifications/Awards**

Necklace Awardee | 2018 - 2019 Ring Awardee | 2019 - 2020

TESDA Computer Systems Servicing NCII Passer

Speaker – Front End Web Development Fundamentals Workshop